http://www.megadox.com/privacy-policy

Blog
(0)
items
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Privacy Policy
Last updated May 2018The following privacy policy discloses how MegaDox.com gathers, processes and uses personal information collected on this website. We use your information based on your consent. Your use of this website indicates that you agree to the collection, disclosure and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Personal Information Collected From Your Account and Purchases
When you create an account with MegaDox.com, or when you make a purchase through our website, you provide the following personal information:
your name, address, phone number and email address;
credit card information each time a purchase is made (we do not store your credit card details in our system);
account preferences, including your consent to receive our newsletter or other offers;
from our corporate and business customers, the name(s) and title(s) of the person(s) authorized to use the account.
This information is collected and used for the following purposes:
To establish and maintain a commercial relationship with you and to provide you with products and services. Personal contact and credit card information is required to process your purchases. We use your account information to identify you when you log in, to allow you to set up and access your account and download forms and documents which you have purchased. This information is used only for these purposes and is only retained in transaction records required for internal management and auditing purposes, unless you provide your express consent for some other use or unless we are required by law to allow a court or other third party to access it.
To understand your needs and preferences. We maintain a record of the products and services you receive from us, and we may ask you for additional information so that we can serve you better.
To provide you with information you have requested. Your email address will be used to send you our newsletters and mailings ONLY WITH YOUR EXPRESS CONSENT. You can provide this consent when you set up your account. You can withdraw your consent for such mailings at any time.
To develop, enhance or provide new products and services. We may from time to time conduct surveys and research, requesting input from our visitors to help us improve our website, products and services in an effort to serve you better. Your participation in such surveys is voluntary, and in some cases you may have the option to participate anonymously. However, your name, address, email and telephone number may be required to take advantage of bonuses or other benefits which are available to survey participants, in which case your contact information will only be used for notification and fulfillment purposes.
To manage and administer our business. Our server logs record statistical information, such as visitors' IP addresses, type of operating systems, time and duration of visit, web pages requested, and identify visitors by categories such as domains and browser types. These statistics are used strictly for internal informational purposes on an aggregate basis and they do not contain any personal identifying information (name, address, etc).
To meet legal, regulatory, security and processing requirements (such as in response to a court order), and otherwise as permitted or required by law.
If we intend to use personal information for purposes not identified to you or as set out above, these other purposes will be described to you at the time that we collect the information and prior to any use being made of that information. We will not use your information for any other purpose without your express consent.
Personal Information Collected from Emails and Social Media
When you share or comment on a page of our website via social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc., the social media site may make certain information available from your profile, such as your email address, profile picture and friends list. We also collect information you submit in reviews, comments and in emails to us.
This information will be treated by us in the same manner that all other personal information is treated, and the terms of this Privacy Policy apply to all information gathered and passed off to MegaDox.com from such sites.
Information Collected from Cookies and Web Tracking Software
We employ the use of tools such as browser "cookies" and web tracking tools such as Google Analytics to collect information about users. These tools do not gather personal identifying information. They simply tell us which browser and device you are using to access the website, which pages of our website you visited, which website you came from and where you go next.
You should be aware that MegaDox.com cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for MegaDox.com. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you can turn off cookies in your browser; however, you should note that you must have cookies enabled in your browser if you wish to make a purchase on the MegaDox.com website, log into your account or download files.
Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies or block tracking. The options you select are browser and device specific and may not work in all instances.
Third Party Access to Information
We may share information with third parties who perform certain functions on our behalf, such as providing marketing assistance, analyzing data, preparing and maintaining site content, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These agents have access to customer information only as required in order to help them perform their functions on our behalf, but they are not allowed to use that information for any unlawful purpose and must keep such information confidential and not act in violation of any applicable privacy laws.
We also work closely with our affiliates, and in some cases we offer services or sell documents jointly with these affiliates. When you purchase documents or services that are provided jointly by MegaDox.com and one of its affiliates, we share our customer information with that affiliate with respect to your purchase.
MegaDox.com may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through our website. MegaDox.com is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties, and you should check the applicable privacy policy of such party before providing personally identifiable information.
MegaDox.com will release customer information to the appropriate law enforcement, governmental or other authorities if legally required to do so. MegaDox.com will also release such information if we feel it is necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of our customers, affiliates, partners or any other party and for purposes of protection from fraud and credit risk.
MegaDox.com is not in the business of selling customer information to others. Our customer information is not available for sale to any outside entity. Customer information is a valuable business asset. If for any reason MegaDox.com transfers or divests itself of its business assets, all relevant customer information will be transferred as part of those business assets.
External Links
The MegaDox.com website contains links or references to other websites to which this privacy policy does not apply. These sites are not owned or controlled by MegaDox.com, and MegaDox.com is not responsible for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information or the privacy practices of other organizations or other websites to which our site may refer visitors or provide links for. When submitting personal information on such other websites, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of those sites.
Security
This site has security measures in place (including the use of Secure Socket Layers ("SSL") encryption technology) to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the personal information under our control. All order forms are encrypted and are transmitted via a secure server. However, the Internet is not 100% secure and we cannot guarantee that your use of our website will be completely safe and without risk. Please use caution and ensure that you safeguard and protect your passwords.
We store customer information, including log-in and password information, on our website in a secure manner. We store such information in a manner not accessible to Web browsers, behind firewall and password protection, or offline. We keep personal information only as long as necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy and as otherwise required by law. After such time the personal information is deleted from our servers and will only remain in the backups on such servers until such time as those backups are overwritten and replaced.
Employees, agents and affiliates of MegaDox.com who require access to your personal information in order to fulfill their job or contractual requirements will have access to your personal information to the extent necessary to fulfill such requirements.
Updating Your Account Information
If you wish to update your personal information, log into your account to access your account profile and make changes online.
Your Consent
We will not send you any promotional emails, newsletters or marketing materials of any kind without your express consent to receive such materials. However, when you make a purchase from our website, we will send you a receipt for such purchase by email, and any followup written communication with you will be via email. Please note that this is the only delivery method for transaction receipts. We do not mail or fax receipts.
We will not send you newsletters, offers, site updates or any other emails unless you expressly request that we do so. If at any time you wish to opt out of any mailing list that you have subscribed to, you may do so by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link in the email. You can also change your contact preferences by logging into your account and updating your profile.
You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of personal information at any time, however, please note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your personal information, we may no longer be able to provide certain of our products or services.
MegaDox.com does not collect, use or disclose your personal information other than as described in this privacy policy without your consent, unless permitted or required by law. We may be required or permitted under statute or regulation to collect, use or disclose personal information without your consent, for example in response to a court order or subpoena, to comply with local, provincial or federal regulations, or to collect a debt owed to us.
How to Contact Us
This website is subject to the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA). This legislation closely regulates our handling of your personal information. You can find more information on this Act through the Government of Canada website. You have a right to know what information we have on file about you. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, or if you would like to review your personal information, you can contact us by email at info@megadox.com, or you can write us at the following address:
MegaDox.comPO Box 34066, Westbrook PO1610 - 37 Street SWCalgary, AB, CanadaT3C 3W2ATTENTION: Privacy Officer
If you are not satisfied with our response to your privacy concerns, you may wish to contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner through their website or by calling 1-800-267-0441.
This website is intended to be used by persons who have reached the legal age of consent. We do not knowingly collect personal information from minors. If you believe that your child has given us personal information, please contact us via email or at the address given above.
Any dispute arising between the customer and MegaDox.com with respect to privacy is subject to the terms and conditions of use and this privacy policy, including limitations on damages, arbitration and application of the laws of the Province of Alberta, Canada.
Updates to Privacy Policy
The foregoing policies are effective as of May 31, 2018. MegaDox.com reserves the right to update this privacy policy at any time by posting the policy changes on our website. Site visitors are advised to periodically check this website for such changes.
Information
Glossary
Find a Lawyer
Legal In A Box
Privacy Policy
About MegaDox
Customer service
Frequently Asked Questions
info@megadox.com
Copyright © 2020 MegaDox. All rights reserved.
Powered by nopCommerce
Our site uses cookies so that we can remember you and provide you with an enhanced user experience. If you do not agree with our use of cookies, please change the cookie settings in your web browser.
I Accept
Learn more ~
How To Block Cookies
